Hello everyone!
I am in the Genji section!
I am Ryouto Nakano!
I'm Jun Muto!
Today!
Hashtag
Question to Genjibu!
Foxy Grape Edition!
Oh!
So...
Yes ...
We received this from all of you!
Questions about the 3rd single
I will answer the questions about Foxy Grape
I will answer them.
Oh!
That's nice.
Yes, it is.
Since the single was released
We've been running through the summer tour.
Yes, good.
I'm sure you observers
I'm sure you've heard a lot of it.
So let's get right to the questions, shall we?
Oh!
Question one.
I had the impression that there were many songs that seemed difficult to sing again.
They were difficult, weren't they?
Were there any songs that were particularly difficult to record?
All of them were difficult again in terms of rhythm.
It was difficult.
Especially Foxy Grape.
There are some unique parts to the rhythm.
But that's the point.
I could hear the instruments
with the instruments in the background
to the instruments behind the instruments
I like it.
Rhythm was very difficult, wasn't it?
And the work was very fast.
That's right.
Godshaka was also surprisingly difficult.
There was a lot of tension.
The members' songs changed from one to another in a flash.
It's fast, and it's high, and it's high, and it's high.
Also, I felt like I was in a game world.
That's for sure.
Godshaka especially, Natsumi, Hen, and Naisaga Oke.
Is that a ballad?
It's a ballad, like a minium ballad.
The rhythm of that one was pretty difficult.
I like the theme, too.
Do you have any difficult songs? I mean...
All of them.
I'm a foxy grape.
My rhythm...
I think I'd have to say Godshagga.
I'm Godshagga, and I'm pretty sure Doshagar was difficult.
That's how it was.
The second question.
In reference to Foxy Grape, what are some of the members' great qualities that make you jealous?
I see...
Foxy Grape is a song in itself.
It comes from something sour or "dame".
It's about being jealous of people.
It's about being jealous of the members.
I was jealous of the members, and I missed them, well, the members,
I think it was a good thing that I was jealous of the members.
There are so many good things about the members.
There were so many that I don't know where to start.
I don't know where to start.
I think you are a wonderful human being, Jun,
I think.
I don't like it,
Oh, so that's how it is.
I knew it,
You are a wonderful human being, you know,
You have a beautiful heart.
Oh, wow. I'm a little jealous of you.
I think it's your strong point.
I'm still Kanami-kun.
I'm sorry.
I knew it.
Your voice is low and your body is soft.
You're soft.
I don't have a very flexible body.
I'm not very flexible.
When I sing a song, it's usually
I have a higher energy than when I sing.
I can take what I don't have.
I envy you a lot.
I think the rest of the band is great.
Question three.
What is your favorite prop from the Foxy Grape music video set?
Do you have a favorite prop from the Foxy Grape music video set?
I thought the stage set was really nice.
I'd like to know if you have a favorite part of this set.
Yes, the set was amazing, wasn't it?
Yes, it was.
It was the most elaborate set I've ever seen.
There were a lot of props.
The pavilion and the jungle were fused together, weren't they?
That's true.
I'm a fox.
That's right.
You know... as the title says...
I'm a fox.
I'm sure many of you know this.
On the list of favorite animals...
I'm number one.
Oh, you mentioned that.
Yes, because it's an animal.
I really, really want to have that one.
I've been looking at it for a long time.
You were talking to it.
We were playing with it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, it was fun.
Yeah, that's it.
I was, I was, uh...
When we got to the chorus, when we got to the whole picture.
I see that flamingo at the end of the picture.
Oh...
The pink one.
On the far left.
I like that pink.
It's a little assertive, but it's on the edge.
Yes, yes, yes.
Take a good look at it, everyone.
Look forward to it.
Question four.
You all are like the fox in the sourpuss
Have you ever given up on something
Have you ever given up on something that was out of your reach?
I don't care if it's a small thing.
Which ones?
Basketball's hot.
Can I talk about basketball?
When I was in the third grade.
I played basketball for my club.
Dunking.
I really wanted to try it.
When I dunked, I would just...
You know...
You see the red ring?
Yes, sir.
I can already reach it.
Wow, that's great!
Jump!
Yes, sir.
I've been working on that kind of jumping ability.
And I thought I could dunk it.
I thought I could dunk.
That's right.
I've been jumping all the time.
Flying.
Fly, fly, fly
Ketto to ketto ketto koko
Oh, this ain't a sound single!
Oh, sorry, sorry.
vegetarian
Yes, Shintaro Nanase
Listen to that one too.
Please listen to it.
No, yeah, really.
Yeah, I've flown over it a bunch of times.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It didn't work.
That's when I gave up.
I don't like to give up in life.
The only thing I gave up on was...
I thought, "I'm going to go out today.
I thought, "I'm going out today.
I thought...
I thought, "Why don't I just stay in bed?
And I spent the rest of the day saying that.
Wow, I've had that.
I've beaten myself up like that before.
But that's a happy holiday.
It's a happy holiday.
The fifth question
The lyrics of "Natsuno ni tohen daikaku daikaku daikaku" are
I really wanted you to smile only at me
What was that?
I wanted you to smile only at me
I like it because I can really relate to it.
What are your favorite lyrics in the lyrics of "Natsuno to Tou Hen Dai Sangakuan" by local residents, and what are your favorite lyrics in the lyrics of "Natsu no Hi to New Year's Day" by Harajuku residents?
What are your favorite lyrics?
When winter comes
I'll see the star hermitage again
By then, I'm sure
It'll be too late.
And there
There's a lot of power building up.
I mean, you'll notice.
This song has a main character.
And he's in love with someone that doesn't come true.
And the lyrics are a little sad.
And then, at the very end...
I wonder if I can still do it.
Is it a scene where he realizes that he can still do it?
Yes, indeed.
It's too late to do it like this.
I think...
Well, here's the lyrics I'm singing.
The first chorus is still too long for me to tell you.
It's still too long
But by the last chorus, it's too early to tell.
There you go.
I knew it. And the passage of time, too.
Well, it's easy to take off, isn't it?
When it first starts, it feels like a long time
But when it's over in the blink of an eye...
It's the passage of time.
or the change of the main character's mind...
I really like the lyrics.
I really like that part of the lyrics.
That's for sure.
Question 6
From that moment on, I was, uh, captivated by it. Yes.
This song has a lot of distinctive lyrics,
What is your favorite lyric or phrase from the local brass?
You really have a lot of lyrics, now, don't you?
It's been a long time since I've heard it.
But I can say that I like Asphalt's favorite lyrics,
1B or 2B,
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That flow,
They all just sing one word each.
Ah.
That's how they think in the old days.
There's the Genji blast and all that.
Well, each of them has their own individuality, and that's where you can suddenly feel it.
I think I like the B-melody.
If you don't have a life, eat bread.
Why?
No, I bought Marie Antoninade.
I know the lyrics.
I know.
The lyrics.
Yes, yes, yes
Yes, yes, yes, lyrics, I like sweets, so I bought some Marie & Manet lyrics, I know, lyrics
Yes, yes, yes, yes
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, lyrics
Sweets, I like sweets
I like candy, candy, candy
Barry & Manet
That's right.
That's how some people are.
That's how I feel.
Question seven.
Next up.
"Dienpathy.
The lyrics were very grand and pushy!
I could see everyone there singing on the big stage.
I was really moved!
What is your favorite part of the song, or favorite lyrics, as chosen by the locals?
Next, Jimmy Empathy's "I'm a believer" for me!
I see.
Belief is everything.
That's so true!
That's the one.
I'm a believer.
I see.
I've always been the only one who can screw up, the brave one.
Uh, yeah.
I knew it was a no-brainer.
We're all dreaming boys now, aren't we?
That's what I think, too.
If you don't try, there's no winning or losing.
There is no such thing as giving up.
I thought the lyrics were very encouraging.
It's a lyric that really pushes me forward.
What did you think of the first question and the last one?
Also, since it is a hidden self-introduction song based on your interviews, were there any stories you told that were used in the song?
For those of you who don't know, there is a song called Gotshakari Hip Hop,
Let me also explain my hidden self-introduction.
There is a song called Gotshaga Hip Hop.
It's called "Hide and Seek Koushagami".
It's a song about the episodes we've been talking about.
and also episodes that we have never told before.
The lyrics of the song are interspersed with episodes that we've never mentioned.
I haven't told you which episodes they are yet, but I'm sure you can guess which episodes they are.
I haven't told you which episode it is yet, but you can imagine it. I haven't told you yet. Well, imagine...
I'm sure you can guess whose episode this is.
I think I can figure it out.
Do you have it?
I don't think so.
Seriously, Mr. Ishida and I...
We talked too much.
I was the first one to sing him to sleep.
Jex sang...
Yes, sir.
Um...
I think you're a super narcissist.
Super narcissism!
Yes...
So, you take Kazu anytime, anywhere, that's super narcissism, right, Tokai-san?
So, whenever and wherever...
You know...
I'm a guy who pursues coolness.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'm always looking at myself...
Find a mirror or something.
I see. I see.
As a bath-conscious man.
Yes.
I check it every waking moment.
That's where Juke used to be.
Yes, yes, yes... tell me that.
Ryota can sleep anywhere.
Yes, he can sleep anywhere
Yes, yes, yes, even now
Even in a place like this?
Yes, yes.
I can even sleep in a car on a bumpy mountain road.
The easiest place to sleep.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
So you can drink as much as you want, but...
But it says it's against the law.
I see.
I was tired.
I'm... I'm...
Some kind of gummy deal.
We're a real-life club.
Like, if one of us buys gummy bears, everyone is allowed to eat them.
It's like an unspoken agreement.
Chris told me about that episode.
So we made a contract for gummy bears.
I think the "anyways" part is my story.
I think that's my story.
I guess it's like that.
I really appreciate all the questions and comments, and I'd like to say thank you very much.
Thank you very much for all your questions and comments.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for watching our music video.
Thanks to all of you who shot the video 400,000 times.
Wow!
We've passed the 400,000th shot!
Thank you very much!
It really is a disc full of colorful songs!
Yes, sir.
I hope you will continue to love our third single
I hope you love Foxy Grape!
I'm so happy, I'm so happy!
See you again somewhere!
Bye bye!
Looking forward to new songs!